Amy Potter

Albertville, MN, 55301

GitHub: /potteramy | Portfolio : https://potteramy.github.io/portfolio-react/

Entry-level full-stack web developer utilizing years as a freelance artist to think outside the box with a desire for life-long learning. Has teamwork experience in groups to make full stack web applications. Dedicated to problem solving, communication, task management, and creativity.

EDUCATION

Full Stack Web Development Certificate - University of Minnesota Minneapolis, MN June 2023

Associates of Liberal Arts - Minneapolis Community and Technical College Minneapolis, MN May 2020

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Javascript, HTML, CSS, MERN stack: MongoDB, Express.js, Node.js, React.js; GitHub, GitBash, Mongoose, JQuery, Bootstrap, Heroku, responsive design, local storage, session storage, user authentication, GraphQL

EXPERIENCE

Freelance Artist 2015 - Present

- Dedication to learning new skills
- Exercises perceptual reasoning and problem solving daily
- Communicates with clients to assess expected aesthetic and timeline for proposed commissions

Parkway Pizza St. Louis Park, MN — Server March 2022 - Present

- Attention to detail
- Task management
- Conflict resolution

University of Minnesota Advanced Research and Diagnostic Laboratory Minneapolis, MN- Senior Laboratory Technician November 2020- February 2022

- Receiving, ordering, processing and performing inventory laboratory samples according to procedure
- Delegating tasks to students to fulfill study orders in a timely manner
- Written and verbal communication with study coordinators and point persons
- Navigating Laboratory Information System (STARLims)

VOLUNTEER WORK

Event Coordinator Earth Day Gathering 2022- Resilient Earth non-profit and Green Crescent Acres Farm

• Planning, community engagement, task delegation, flier design, logo design, conflict resolution